[
    {
      "question": "What is the mean of these numbers:<br> [91, 92, 93, 94, 95, 96, 97, 98, 99]?",
      "correctAnswer": "95",
      "options": [
        "94",
        "95",
        "96",
        "97"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mean of these numbers:<br> [92, 93, 94, 95, 96, 97, 98, 99, 100]?",
      "correctAnswer": "96",
      "options": [
        "95",
        "96",
        "97",
        "98"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mean of these numbers:<br> [93, 94, 95, 96, 97, 98, 99, 100, 101]?",
      "correctAnswer": "97",
      "options": [
        "96",
        "97",
        "98",
        "99"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mean of these numbers:<br> [94, 95, 96, 97, 98, 99, 100, 101, 102]?",
      "correctAnswer": "98",
      "options": [
        "97",
        "98",
        "99",
        "100"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mean of these numbers:<br> [95, 96, 97, 98, 99, 100, 101, 102, 103]?",
      "correctAnswer": "99",
      "options": [
        "98",
        "99",
        "100",
        "101"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mean of these numbers:<br> [96, 97, 98, 99, 100, 101, 102, 103, 104]?",
      "correctAnswer": "100",
      "options": [
        "99",
        "100",
        "101",
        "102"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mean of these numbers:<br> [97, 98, 99, 100, 101, 102, 103, 104, 105]?",
      "correctAnswer": "101",
      "options": [
        "100",
        "101",
        "102",
        "103"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mean of these numbers:<br> [98, 99, 100, 101, 102, 103, 104, 105, 106]?",
      "correctAnswer": "102",
      "options": [
        "101",
        "102",
        "103",
        "104"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mean of these numbers:<br> [99, 100, 101, 102, 103, 104, 105, 106, 107]?",
      "correctAnswer": "103",
      "options": [
        "102",
        "103",
        "104",
        "105"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mean of these numbers:<br> [100, 101, 102, 103, 104, 105, 106, 107, 108, 109]?",
      "correctAnswer": "104",
      "options": [
        "103",
        "104",
        "105",
        "106"
      ]
    }
]